// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the measure of tendency to resist flowing motion?",
    answer: "B. Viscosity",
    options: [
      "A. Capillary action",
      "B. Viscosity",
      "C. Surface tension",
      "D. Vapor Pressure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the energy required to change exactly one gram of liquid to vapor at its normal boiling point?",
    answer: "A. Molar heat of vaporization",
    options: [
      "A. Molar heat of vaporization",
      "B. Capillary action",
      "C. Surface tension",
      "D. Viscosity"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the amount of energy required to stretch or increase the surface of a liquid by a unit area?",
    answer: "C. Surface tension",
    options: [
      "A. Capillary action",
      "B. Viscosity",
      "C. Surface tension",
      "D. Vapor Pressure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What term defines the tendency of a liquid to rise in narrow tubes or be drawn into small openings and a result of intermolecular attraction between the liquid and solid materials?",
    answer: "A. Capillary action",
    options: [
      "A. Capillary action",
      "B. Viscosity",
      "C. Surface tension",
      "D. Vapor Pressure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the property of liquid that is exerted by a vapor in equilibrium state?",
    answer: "D. Vapor Pressure",
    options: [
      "A. Capillary action",
      "B. Viscosity",
      "C. Surface tension",
      "D. Vapor Pressure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What property of liquid does the temperature at which the vapor pressure of a liquid is equal to the external pressure?",
    answer: "D. Boiling point",
    options: [
      "A. Molar heat of vaporization",
      "B. Capillary action",
      "C. Surface tension",
      "D. Boiling point"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the intermolecular attraction present between like molecules (the liquid molecules)?",
    answer: "B. Cohesion",
    options: [
      "A. Adhesion",
      "B. Cohesion",
      "C. Capillary action",
      "D. Viscosity"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What attraction happens between unlike molecules (such as those in water and in the particles that make up the glass tube)?",
    answer: "A. Adhesion",
    options: [
      "A. Adhesion",
      "B. Cohesion",
      "B. Cohesion",
      "D. Viscosity"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the relationship between intermolecular forces of attraction and the vapor pressure of a liquid?",
    answer: "C. The stronger the intermolecular forces of attraction the lower the vapor pressure of a liquid.",
    options: [
      "A. The stronger the intermolecular forces of attraction the higher the vapor pressure of a liquid.",
      "B. The weaker the intermolecular forces of attraction the higher the vapor pressure of a liquid.",
      "C. The stronger the intermolecular forces of attraction the lower the vapor pressure of a liquid.",
      "d. None of the choices"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Liquids that have ____ intermolecular forces also have ____ surface tension.",
    answer: "A. Liquids that have strong intermolecular forces also have high surface tension.",
    options: [
      "A. Liquids that have strong intermolecular forces also have high surface tension.",
      "B. Liquids that have weak intermolecular forces also have high surface tension.",
      "C. Liquids that have strong intermolecular forces also have low surface tension.",
      "d. None of the choices"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];